- Is it too much?
- Not if you're a rugby team.
By the way, you didn't join us
because you stuffed yourself...
...with a chicken-carbonara sub
at Quizno's.
(Sheldon:)Why would I join you?
(Leonard:)No reason.
Oh, you know what?
Maybe this isn't such a good idea.
Oh, no, well, now,
there's always the possibility...
...that alcohol and poor judgment
on her part...
(Sheldon:)...might lead to a nice romantic evening.
You're right. Alcohol, poor judgment.
It could go well.
(Sheldon:)Of course, there's the other possibility
that this day kicks off...
...an unpleasant six months of you
passing awkwardly in the hall...
(Sheldon:)...until one of you breaks down
and moves to another zip code.
(Leonard:)You could have stopped at,
"It could go well."
If I could have, I would have.
(Leonard:)I mean, I'm a perfectly nice guy.
There's no reason...
(Leonard:)...we couldn't go to the restaurant
and have a lovely dinner.
(Leonard:)Maybe take a walk afterwards,
talk about things we have in common.